Some.
Or the default.
Right, yeah.
But here, in this particular design,
you have three line items,
but it is when you collapse, right,
when you shrink this one,
Mm-hmm.
it is showing two,
it should show only one line.
Okay, so it should show only one line.
The first line, right?
And that's why you have a plus.
Hmm.
The plus is to say that there are
additional lines to it.
Okay,
there are many more things up below here.
Yeah, more than one. Yeah,
say more than one.
Okay.
That is why you're just giving an option
so that you click and see.
Okay, I gotcha.
For that particular order, 74 M, right?
You see what you are having here is you
Huh.
are having order 74 M, 74 M,
and then the third one is 75 M.
If it is a second order,
then it should be a separate by itself,
right?
There should be either A plus or just one
item to show. See.
Each order will have its own number of
lines.
Okay, get shorter.
Are you getting it right?
Each order will have its own line. I have,
say, in a shipment,
shipment is a combination of 1 order or
multiple orders.
Uh-huh.
Huh?
right? One order or more than one order,
right? If there is only one order,
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
one order can have one line or it can
have more than one line.
In order to have online, yeah, exactly.
But if you look at your model right here,
the diagram, it shows that 74 M, 74 M,
and the third line within the same minus
is 75 M. It cannot be like that.
Right, you can group 74 M together, right?
74 M has line one and line 2.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
75 M maybe has only one line.
Right, 76 M.
Yeah, right.
Right now, this is different though,
right? Yeah.
Ah, right.
So it should not be together with 74M.
It should be a separate one.
Mm.
Okay,
I will put another colour to
differentiate because that's bringing
confusion. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
If it's too many,
it's going to bring confusion. Okay.
Yeah, and one one suggestion, right?
Then say the say design-wise, it's fine,
but if you go back to this one, right?
See, you selected a shipment.
You selected shipment 448, correct?
Geta.
Mm-hmm.
But you are showing only one order,
but there are three orders here, right?
Do you see that inconsistency exists in
the model, right? You show only one.
Order, but in the design,
but there are in the product section,
Mhm.
you have three orders.
Yeah.
Yeah, just make it consistent, right?
So if you have just for one line,
if you are demonstrating one or two
examples,
just make those examples consistent.
If you say count of order count,
No.
you see there only one. But here,
the order count under the product section,
you have three orders, right? 74 M, 75 M,
and 76 M.
So, they are not consistent.
Yeah,
they should be consistent to what I was
looking here, right?
It.
Right. So when you have the order,
you just say instead of 49 AM,
make it 74 AM, 75 AM, and 75 76 AM, right?
So that you can make,
you are making it consistent.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah.
Because someone looking at it, right,
might not get the picture.
Why there is only one order,
but here you're showing three orders.
Okay.
Okay, we open it.
I.
Okay.
****.
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah, this table is pretty long.
You have too many attributes here.
Yeah.
Yeah. See,
the main thing that they will look into
is the volume, the count,
and all those things.
So just see that the data is consistent
between the lines being selected and the
total that comes out for this particular
orders altogether, right?
A shipment is a collection of orders.
If say, for example, in this case, right,
Jha.
the package count comes out to be
100, 105, 105 plus 80 is 185, right?
185 bags or 185, this one.
Mm-hmm.
The same count should be there at the
shipment level.
It should say the shipment has 185 bags
or boxes.
You're putting bags and boxes together,
right? Just make it a little easy for us.
right? Say that it is all back, all boxes,
so that it's easy for us to show them,
right?
We don't have to make it complicated here.
It's just an idea, correct?
Okay.
Perfect.
Um, let's go to the next.
And again, you will not have, yeah,
you will not have a mix of weights.
Say you are here, you are having LBs,
right? All will be in LB, right?
In pounds. Similarly, a package will be,
let's keep it all constant, right? Boxes,
Mhm.
you know,
pallets or bags or whatever it is.
Don't put boxes,
drums and bags because then it might be.
little difficult for us to show certain
information.
Yeah, so this will be,
but the description could be different,
right? Because this is a different item.
Yeah, description can be different. Yeah,
that is fine. Description is different,
but I'm saying the package, right?
So only a few things like here you made
Yeah.
the volume consistent, right?
It's all in cubic feet.
It is in pounds and tare weights in
pounds. Don't mix pounds and kgs, right?
Don't mix pounds and maybe metric tons.
Mhm.
Don't do that.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Okay, perfect.
Great.
Let's go with the next one.
This is the routing guides.
Yeah.
Yeah, correct.
This is all the options,
and here is your explanation of what it
it look it used to look like, right?
I gave you the second file, right?
I gave you the second file.
That's what how it needs to be.
Okay, give me a second.
It is here, I'm not wrong.
Give me one second.
Iris.
Odyssey.
I think it's this one.
Yes, this is how it needs to be, yeah.
Yeah, this is it.
And so we are in routing and where is
routing?
Here, right? This one. Ah, okay.
Let me see.
Yeah.
Connects.
I see.
OK,
I didn't like my mind didn't click on
this one,
so I need to review it once again because
Correct, yeah.
I only use this.
And obviously you always want to use your
grid.
These 3 lines, okay.
And let's cheque this.
So the first thing that I knew is that
the each line is an option,
Yeah.
so it's selectable.
Correct. Each line is an option.
It should be selectable.
Then you have routing guide, status,
pick up, okay, pick up, pick up hours,
pick up this one, delivery date, okay,
complete backup.
Primary group, primary, okay, okay,
but this one needs to be modified
accordingly to those design that I gave
you earlier, right? The second design,
that's how it needs to be, right?
Because when the user would want to see
Mhm.
Mm.
what are all the routing options
available.
to them, they should be able to see it,
how they would want their, yeah,
Mhm.
this is how they would want to see that.
So you want to see everything at once,
right?
Exactly, right? See,
what you did is right.
Alright.
The tables are fine,
but you need to put the headers the same
way.
Then we need to add specific tabs
underneath it, right? If you go back,
within the routing guide, right,
you will have multiple tabs here.
Routing option, then, yeah,
Yes.
there are four to five tabs, right?
There are five tabs there.
So we need to add those tabs and there
Yeah.
are action buttons within those.
Then there are certain few that action
Yeah.
for shipments,
so action for shipment options for each
of those options, right?
And then there are some information at
Mm.
the header level.
Okay,
I just like to know a quick description
of routing options, thus.
My guess is this is the way you are
taking action over your planification,
right? So is this for that as well?
Because since...
I didn't get your point.
Can you say that again?
Like I like to understand what this
routing options table is not just for
displaying information, right?
It's also for taking action.
Yeah, they will have to take action.
Correct. User will take an action. See,
Yeah.
as I told you, right,
the shipment idea is to find a carrier.
Exactly. Okay. Okay.
Right.
Right? So the options are nothing,
but I have multiple carrier options,
which carrier I would want to select,
right?
The system automatically selects or the
user will be able to select their own
carrier and tender to that carrier.
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
Tender means it is like sending that
information to the carrier, right?
I Geta.
Mhm.
The carrier can accept it or carrier can
reject it. Say like, hey,
I'm already booked for that day, right?
I cannot do anything. They can decline.
Mm.
So in that case, if they decline,
you go to the next option available.
Okay.
Got it. So...
Yeah.
That comes to another question that I
have.
Mmh.
Here you have shipments, exceptions,
right? So, this, this,
Yeah.
this whole this whole domain is all is is
on the first go is showing you exceptions,
errors, right?
Exactly.
So, based on errors,
the user is trying to plan, right?
Yeah, they should take an action.
Say the first one is exceptions.
Plan its.
The system is not able to proceed by
itself. See,
the whole objective is to make the system
work by itself, right? Find a carrier,
Hmm.
do this, send them, update,
all those things.
But there are certain instances where the
system will not be able to proceed.
Where?
do certain things by itself.
It would require someone's intervention
Uh-uh.
to guide the system, right?
So what do you need to do next?
Yeah.
So that is when it comes and sits in the
exception.
Oh, okay.
If the system can do everything by itself,
it will go in monitoring, right?
It is just for the user to monitor.
The system is doing by itself a lot of
Mm.
things, and it is just monitoring.
If the user would want to see, like, okay,
if the customer calls and says, like,
okay, well, what happened to my shipment?
And it might be in monitoring and it was
like waiting for a carrier,
Yeah.
a carrier to send send us a feedback
saying like they're going to accept it or
not.
So they will look into the monitoring and
then they will tell, okay,
it's maybe just waiting for, you know,
carrier acceptance.
I see.
Yes.
Okay, yeah, that's much clearer now.
Um...
Okay, so let me let me work on that.
I'm sorry.
Then we have a coastal location.
Yeah, cost allocation base, yeah.
Give me a second, let's go here.
So you don't need sell shipment costs.
Here's example and here it is.
So it will give you a summary and then it
will, sorry.
It will show you the...
Yeah, base, discount, fuel, axorial, okay,
total, margin, fantastic. That looks cool,
the header. Then the bottom section, okay,
order, each order allocation, direct cost,
AP cost, base,
Fuel discount, stop of charges,
stop of charges, okay, okay,
then direct cost, AP cost, base cost,
okay, plan completed, plan completed,
do you?
have cost allocation, right? See,
right now you have, what do you say,
AP cost, right?
We might have to do a similar tab for AR
Uh-huh.
cost. A cost is customer cost.
Thanks.
Okay.
Yeah, so we don't have...
Soham.
Don't need sell shipment cost. Okay,
it has been marked as don't need sell
shipment cost. Okay,
one second if you go back to that one.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Yeah,
we need direct shipping cost only if the
Okay.
two loads is in the shipment.
Direct shipping cost should be available
for, see, okay, if you go back to that,
why I'm saying that you might not need it,
because if you go back to your design.
Uh-huh.
Right?
Why I said it is not required here is
because you are still awaiting customer.
Okay.
We might need it, say just like this,
we might have to create a customer cost
related for that.
Why I'm saying that is because initially
we had we had recently had a requirement
where in which the sell side of the
shipment is not going to get created
until by.
or a carrier has been accepted, right?
So that is how we had current logic.
Uh-huh.
That logic is going to get replaced.
They wanted to create the sell side
immediately on creation of the buy side.
Right?
So it means that at any point you have an
A.
AP cost, you also have an AR cost. Right?
Two costs will be available.
Okay.
Right,
so that is where we would also want the
Mhm.
cost to be available for the AP and AR.
Right, similar screen,
if you can create a similar screen for
I don't think.
Mm.
within this cost allocation, right?
If you can create AP cost and a separate
one or insert inside this,
if you can create an AR cost,
that will also be helpful.
Give me a second.
A way to show that, okay,
this is your customer.
Let me see if I have that screen so that
you'll be able to get that idea.
Jha.
Maybe select.
From last time it is not opening for me.
I don't know for some reason.
To do.
Mm.
18.
Thank God Efrain is recording the call.
Yeah, he's already started the recording.
I did see that.
Yep.
Yeah.
I don't have, it's not opening for,
are you able to open the QA screen?
Can you, do you get the access right?
You got the access right.
Oh yeah, give me a second.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll put the link here.
Try to click on that link and it's not
opening for me. That's what, yeah,
if you go to the rating error, right,
whatever you add.
Do you need the portal or the audience?
Yeah, yeah, rating, rating, rating error.
If you go to the rating error screen,
third, yeah.
And then do you have a shipment?
Huh?
You don't see the shipment.
There should be 3, right?
Give me a second, I'm gonna refresh.
No, no, if you go to rating, rating error,
third one.
Oh no, it's not working now.
It was on my cache.
Yeah, this is not working for you either.
Yeah, it's not working for me.
That's right.
So you have it zero like me?
Yeah.
Oh no, yeah that is, yeah.
Oh.
And I refresh it, sorry.
Oh.
What shall we do?
You don't have the same thing here, right?
In ODM?
ODM, we don't have that.
We don't have that ODM, right?
Okay.
So this is okay.
If you go back to your design.
Uh-huh.
Right.
See,
the main idea is there will be some
difference in cost between the AP and the
AR, right? The base,
you're seeing the base is 1000, right?
The fuel is 400.
Jha.
In AP, sorry, in the AR cost, this 1,
500 can be a little higher or a little
less, right? We don't know how it will be.
Ideally,
it should be higher than the AP cost.
AP cost is cost that we give to the
carrier. When we charge to the customer,
we might charge the same rate or we might
charge more than that.
A P cost.
Oh, I see. Okay.
Right,
so how do we show both the cost in the
same page?
AR and AP.
AR and AP, right?
How do we show the same cost?
Say, for example, you have the base rate,
right? You have the discount on the top.
Mm.
Fuel is there. All this is going to be AP,
right? Can you do a similar line to say,
okay, this is your AR,
this is your AP cost or a, you know,
Mm.
Singh.
carrier cost?
And then you can call it AP cost for now
and then the second line or somewhere to
show that what is your AR cost.
Jha.
And do you need to have it side by side?
Or do you can have it separate?
Separate means you are asking separate
tab.
Yeah, exactly, like this, right?
When you change tabs, it changes view,
right? Do you, or do you need...
Yeah, true, but would you,
don't you think comparing cost,
having it on the same,
this one will be better, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cost.
Yeah, accounts receivable,
one is accounts payable.
A PM here.
Conspinable and but users do usually
compare those like they need to see both
at the same time or not.
Ideally, yes.
It will be better for them to see both at
Oh.
the same time.
So that you're saying the 22.3% margin,
right?
The margin is the difference in pricing
Pareek.
between the AP and the AR.
Yeah.
It's about margins and dances, about...
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Little by little,
I am learning more about this.
Yeah.
Okay, so this is a this is the same,
right? You need to have a PNA.
Yeah,
we need planned cost and completed cost.
Planned cost is when we are actually
planning what is the cost available.
Yeah.
Mhm.
You can mark the completed right now as
grey because when you are completed
happens only when you receive a PGI.
Okay, sorry, give me a second.
The option should be there,
but it should be grey and there should
not be any data at this point of time
because completed happens only after you
get a PGI.
Okay,
but it should be then disabled maybe.
Yeah,
it should be grey and there should be no
data.
Okay.
So you just update the plan cost and plan
should have the AP cost and the AR cost.
Show it completed.
So, that.
I should be.
Right on.
So, that is not relevant right now, right?
OK, seeing at the center, yeah,
Yeah.
so this is not relevant that right now,
because it's after the...
The PGR, right?
PGI. Yeah, PGI. Yeah, correct.
Sorry, BGIBGI.
PGI or PGR, both are same.
Both are related, right? I slash R.
Ahh.
Yeah, correct.
Okay.
Great.
Okay, let's see the second, the next one.
Then what about the here,
the instructions? This is for the...
Instructions, order. Yeah, fantastic.
That's cool.
All the order instructions are here,
right? That's all.
Mm.
Maybe we can collapse it.
Yeah,
if you can collapse it and then show,
Maybe.
that's also good. The first line,
just like how we have it for orders,
the order lines, right?
So the first line is always visible and
Mm.
when there are multiple ones,
you just click and open it.
Okay, I see.
Perfect.
History, I don't have it here yet,
and the documents - this is broken,
I think.
Give me one second.
Yeah.
So, instructions then,
then the documents part.
Instructions, yeah, documents, documents,
you have a BOL, PDF, okay, invoice.
And.
How would they upload it, right? Invoice,
I don't think invoice will be there.
So you, okay, just for example,
you have given, instructions, yeah,
others, wait, certificate, yeah.
Cool, that's cool. Yeah,
upload attachments, right?
Mm.
Can you click on upload attachments? Yeah,
BOL, choose file. Yeah, that's it.
That's it,
because you can select here the
Yeah.
difference one here.
Yeah, others and then get right.
I will try to put this model here then,
in the middle of the screen,
so it's not very like...
Yeah, maybe,
maybe it should when someone is trying to
On the para.
upload it, just it expands and goes up.
Okay, everything, right? Yeah, good idea.
Yeah, and then once they are done,
it comes back to its normal position.
Yeah,
that's better because we forget about
this background.
Yeah.
And.
To.
OK.
And then notes? Oh, I don't have it yet.
Yeah, notes are going to be internal,
that's all. Yeah.
Yeah.
See, once you create the screen,
the second metrics, right?
Okay.
If you go to the top, expand metrics,
right? Expand metrics. Yeah,
the monitoring is going to be very
similar, right? It's not any, if you,
once you design all these screens,
all these screens are going to look
exactly the same.
Hmm,
so we can put the same thing with
Right.
Yeah, yeah, different data monitoring.
You will have a carrier that has been
different data atomic, OK?
waiting. Maybe if you go to,
say for example,
you can just show one example. Maybe like,
what do you do? Approved, approved.
Huh.
You just click on approved and show that,
okay, maybe we can say during the.
A presentation saying like approved,
approved is nothing but a carrier has
accepted it, right?
So we just say that in the tender screen,
instead of being sent,
you will say accept it. That's all.
Okay, I see.
Right,
so you're just tweaking the same
information a little bit in different
stages. That's all.
That is why I'm saying, once you complete,
once you complete this part right,
Okay.
shipment exception,
we can go to monitoring and then tell
Huh?
them that, you know,
it is it's all the same,
but this is how it might look.
Yeah,
you don't need to explain everything
Yeah, yeah, the content-wise,
this is this is the content, right?
after this. Okay.
This is how it looks when the content is
going to look like,
Huh?
and what do you have for actions?
You have certain things in the actions,
right? What are those?
The actions and...
Yeah, right side, next to the export.
Yeah, no, I still need to put it up.
Do you remember we have already the
designer for that?
I just need to implement it here and
Okay.
that's it.
I think this is bad because we used to
have a button instead.
Let me show you. If you remember, no,
this is shipments here, the change field,
right?
Ah, okay.
So, yeah,
I think actions was because we were
thinking with Efrain. Efrain,
are you there?
Yeah, easier.
Yeah.
Okay,
do you remember why we was the idea to
put place an actions button? No,
it's not here, right?
No, I didn't put action.
I only put change a view button. Yeah.
Oh.
Mm.
Yeah, no, then, then...
But anyway, Manuela,
we would need an action button, right?
Say, for example, David raised a point,
what he told me in one of our,
Mm-hmm.
maybe you were not there in the call. Say,
for example, if the user,
there are a few things on the exception,
right? Say, for example,
And.
Where is that? Okay, tender review, right?
So there are two tender reviews.
There should be only one tender review.
But if you are in tender review and the
user goes and clicks on that,
it will display 5 shipments, right?
Mhm.
Ideally, it will display 5 shipments,
right? If the user...
Mm-hmm.
goes and select the five shipments and
can say that go and manually tender all
these.
Okay.
right? Instead of selecting the carrier,
you say it will say that go and tender to
the first carrier or a preferred carrier.
First carrier is always a preferred
carrier, right? Within that option,
the first carrier that appears will be
Mmh.
the preferred carrier.
So if it goes and says if the user wants
to say just tender to everyone,
don't wait for.
tendering time to start,
just go and tender, right?
Then they need an action button where in
which it goes, they click and say like,
okay, you know,
tender to the preferred carriers.
Maybe we can add, keep the action button.
It is to multi-select shipments and do
like, you know,
tender to preferred carrier.
I'll give you maybe one or two.
two options which the user can select to
do it, right?
Uh-huh.
Like tender to preferred carrier, right?
Or we can say cancel all the shipments.
We can say like user can select and
cancel shipments, right?
So that can also be possible.
And what circumstance you would want the
user to cancel shipments.
Uh-huh.
Mm.
That can do.
Yeah.
I see.
Maybe this one can change depending on
the place we are right now, right?
Databricks, exactly which tab we added,
exactly.
Okay, that's a good idea.
I'm going to put it here.
Dynamic actions with.
Okay.
Okay, I think that's it for today.
Right, sure. And yeah,
if you can get these done as soon as
Um, so...
possible, Manuela, then we can, you know,
take it to David and we can review it.
I believe we have a call Wednesday.
If you can get it done by Wednesday,
then we can show David and probably by
this week we can set up a call with
business and review it.
Hopefully, hopefully we can, yeah, I, I,
I...
Yeah.
25th, we have Wednesday, touchpoint,
UX touchpoint, right? Yeah.
Exactly.
I actually asked David to do that because
I feel like their feedback is valuable
too. So I said, hey,
let's do this reviews every week.
So, so they can, yeah,
they they can give us some feedback as
I.
well.
Yeah.
Yeah, hopefully this week. I don't know.
Like, it's really a lot to understand.
Jha.
And yeah,
I don't want to like too much guesswork.
Correct, correct, correct. See,
it requires a lot of understanding as
But okay, it is.
well.
It's not like just like doing some design,
right? It should flow and make sense.
Exactly. One more thing, Janardhana.
After this is approved and you hand it
over to the business,
just be mindful that this doesn't mean it
is done in Figma. We did this.
No, no,
we are not handing over to business.
We are just going to show it to business
saying that this is how it will come out,
right?
And then I will have my own stories for
Yeah.
each of those, right?
Because I need to start putting the
Okay.
stories for each of those. Say,
for example,
I'll start with the three tabs.
I will say there will be a shipment
exception tab,
monitoring tab, PGI tab,
and then what will be under each of those,
Mm.
right?
And then they will have to use your
information, right,
that demo or this mock, what you created,
for them to see, okay, oh,
this is how it is going to look like.
Her.
And then you would start adding colors.
And then, you know,
you would say that exactly this is how
the final output of the UX user interface
is going to be. Say, for example,
maybe you want to give a specific colour
for data issues.
Mhm.
You want to give a specific colour for
this one.
All that user will start going into
details. Right now, it's more a sketch.
No.
Right? We are giving them a more sketch.
And then once we finalize,
Okay, yeah.
we all align on some kind of a sketch,
then I would start drafting the details
around each of those.
And then using those details,
you will refine each of the segments.
You will start with shipment exception,
Right.
then you will work with monitoring.
then PGI, then all the philtre tabs.
Do you want to show the philtre tab?
Then you go in details to make it
consistent across all the sections how
Yeah.
you want to show the philtre tab, right?
So how does it need to look like?
Yeah.
And then next I will put in a story for
search. And under that search,
I will define, say, for example,
we come up with AI kind of a search,
right? Natural language search.
I will say,
Mhm.
AI search and then you will show to the
user how they would be able to search.
OK, yeah, that that.
Right, so that,
so we will go step by step to refine each
of these next, right? Right now,
it is a high-level sketch.
Okay. Perfect.
That was my only concern because to do
the fake math, we need more details.
This is faster. But still,
Exactly.
I would like to start advancing in the
documentation with you.
like I'm going to start writing. I mean,
what I started to do is to write to
little texts about each feature or each
thing or the general idea.
This is what I gave to CloudCut and
everything.
Mhm.
It's not like for Cloud Code,
it's more like for me, for you.
So for example,
you can see here how we are doing things,
right?
So you yourself are like having new ideas
on how to do things as well.
So all of that process needs to be kind
of documented and also.
And that way,
that will help me as well to understand
better.
Yeah, see,
it is already there a little bit.
You can refer to this one and you can
start doing it, right? Say for example,
let me share the epic, right?
That epic has all that information,
Mmh.
what you're asking for, right?
Just give me a second.
Mmh.
Okay.
And if you have if you have any other
documentation that will be helpful as
well.
Yeah.
Paint.
Okay, I'll share my screen for a second,
right?
Then I'll show you which one is that and
then I will paste that link as well.
Yeah.
We'll put that link here.
See,
the link that I pasted was the is the
master epic, right?
So the master epic has all that
Anand.
information, what you're looking for.
It has a high level for your sketch and
all your details.
It has some high level details, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, see, for example,
it tells you what it is.
And then if you go into details by
shipment creation for Odyssey,
one confirmed orders, right?
How does it look like? Then it goes,
if you go and open it,
it'll add a lot of details underneath,
Mmh.
saying like, okay, right,
say load creation and cost retrieval.
Okay.
Right, auto plan evaluation,
then optimization process,
Ohh.
auto tender consideration,
audit and logging, right?
And then what needs to be done in under
all this, right?
So there are details under the UI screens.
If you see here,
Mmh.
I've written some details about UI
screens by shipment listing page,
then it need to have details,
then save search, filters, columns.
So I have given all these details here.
right, in each of those epics, right?
So under this epic,
No.
you will have all those being created.
Then here, if you go to,
then you will have for load related items,
right? So it has a framework.
How does it work?
Right, so if you go here,
so each of this particular epic, 8088,
right?
8088 is the master epic.
Under the master epic,
Yes.
it does all the ones that we would be
building, right?
And each of these will have its own
stories.
I have not started fully writing stories,
but you can see some stories that we have
already started writing.
If you go underneath this one,
Mm.
Okay.
you can see that I have started writing
stories here.
Right, you see all the stories. So,
these are details for this particular
Mm.
epic, right? So, similarly,
I will be adding many stories as I go,
right? As I told you,
we will have to start refining details.
Right now, it is all back in,
so I don't have the front end,
Mhm.
but this gives you an idea saying how the
shipment is.
Supposed to work.
Okay.
Okay, that's important.
And those stories were written for the
Yeah.
future or were written for the backend.
Right now I'm writing only back end.
Once we have an approval from the
Okay.
business saying like, okay, this design,
I like it, right?
I like to proceed with this design.
Then I would start writing the front end
Mhm.
stories, all the UX related stories.
Okay. Okay, yeah, but still I have.
Right now, I'm putting all these,
all these backend related, say,
for example.
have it open, but I can show you.
It's a little more complicated.
I don't know whether you have seen it.
Efrain left.
Okay, maybe he has another call. Okay,
so this is how the shipment domain is
supposed to work, right?
It has a lot of flows. So it'll get,
once an order comes, it'll create a load,
then it'll create a shipment,
then it'll do some optimization,
then it will send to tendering,
Yeah.
then once it sends to tendering,
it has certain other steps.
until the carrier accepts it, right?
So there are so many logics underneath it.
And.
So not every screen will require,
not every logic will require a screen,
right?
It can run back end without even the user
knowing about it, right?
So those are the ones I'm completing
Jha.
right now.
Wherever it requires an user intervention
or a user action,
or the user would want to see.
what the system has done, then I'm,
that is where EDR,
Yeah.
you are coming in and trying to put a
screen together for it.
Okay,
so you are the you are we are doing this
Right.
from starting from the backend and then
Got it.
On it, OK.
Yeah,
back end I'm trying to build so that once
Ohh.
we have the data ready,
we can show it in the front end.
Yeah, okay. Yeah,
this even for the user stories is really
important for because user stories for
front ends mostly are defined by users,
right? We need to define the users.
So it's the.
That is why we need this UX wireframe
ready so that we can talk to the users
Yeah.
and get their approval saying like, okay,
hey, I like this design.
This is coming out well.
So they can give some feedback,
Mm.
then we will go and work on those and,
you know, talk to them again.
Perfect. Okay. That makes...
Thank you for this. I will review it.
But.
I will cheque it.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, okay, Jha.
Yeah.